[EN]And we are rolling!
[CN]我们开录了!
[EN]Jojo Mayer welcome to the Drummers' world
[CN]Jojo Mayer欢迎来到鼓手世界
[EN]And January 20 beenon the road a lot I'm sure.
[CN]今天是1月20号，我知道你最近花了很多时间在外面旅行巡演
[EN]And welcome back to New York, I was just , Now You've been interested in hand development quiet while
[CN]现在欢迎你回到纽约，目前你一直对手部技巧的培养非常有兴趣
[EN]And Now with coming thing, Are you interested in getting invested in the feet develop
[CN]对于接下来的一部教程，你会侧重于对脚部技巧的培养么？
[EN]What's on your mind with the new thing you been working on, you hinted the new DVD coming on about feet technique
[CN]你对手头正在制作的最新教程的理念是什么呢？你提及到将要出品的DVD是关于脚部技巧。
[EN]Well, was not that I'm particularly more interested in it, it's just like right now I'm always have equal have equal interest you know
[CN]这个么..并不是说我是特别对那一想更侧重偏爱。目前我对手脚都是非常有兴趣的
[EN]Oh yes, it's like music, it's like some point, like I realize that
[CN]对了，就拿音乐来说，这就像在某些时候，我忽然会意识到
[EN]There's information missing now so then That kind grab my attention
[CN]这个方面，目前的教材在此是空白。然后才引起我对此的注意力
[EN]So right now
[CN]所以就像现在
[EN]I'm really interesting in a lot of aspects that make compose that bass drum technique, you know
[CN]我对组成地鼓技术的各个要素感兴趣，你知道不单是地鼓技术本身
[EN]Not just technique, I thought to understand that you are trying to understand bass drum technique you have to really understand the way that pedal are made
[CN]并不是单纯的技巧，   我认为你要试图去了解地鼓技巧，你就先要了解踩槌是怎么样构造的
[EN]So I'm currently decomposing bass drum pedals, you know perhaps I'll be able to come up with some original solution that make sense
[CN]所以最近我在拆许多踩槌。你知道或许我能搞出一些大家能觉得有用的原创的东西
[EN]So the idea is the technique of the pedal somehow corresponds technique of the foot is that what you are getting?
[CN]那么就是说踩槌的技巧某种程度上和脚部技巧相关联，这就是你的结论对么？
[EN]Oh, I wound say I mean that's the one way suppose to be really
[CN]哦，我或许会说脚部技巧学习就应该从这里入手，真的
[EN]However , you know most of the pedals we have today or create that mode that was made before 40's and 50's you know
[CN]但是，你知道我们今天所用的大多踩槌的原型都是来自于40或50年代
[EN]Like, I mean most of the pedal we have today are kind reverse engineer mechanical or gretch pedals
[CN]比如说，当今我们用的大多数踩槌都是仿生学设计的机械踩槌
[EN]It was like all the other principles like the speed king, there was a number of different ones, they kind almost vanished in favor of particular pedal
[CN]另外还有一些其他的制作理念，比如ludwig的speed king，还有许多不同的，他们大多因为人们对特定型号的偏爱而退隐江湖了
[EN]Which was really good pedal and really well balance however back in the 50s, drummers play differently you know
[CN]这些都是非常棒的踩槌，非常平衡。而且上溯到50年代，鼓手们演奏也有不同
[EN]They have bigger bass drum with 2 heads，they even to play quiet, not drum out you know
[CN]他们都用大尺寸，前后鼓皮。他们甚至有意更安静的，而不是非常放开踩，你知道的
[EN]everything is changed bass become smaller and front head off, they muffle it
[CN]一切都改变了，地鼓尺寸变小，前皮开洞，鼓手们还要制音
[EN]So they use the same pedal as a interface, so they need to create more volume
[CN]那么如果他们要用同样的踩槌作为脚和鼓的传导媒介，他们就要制造更大的音量
[EN]So they started to bury beat inside the bass drum
[CN]所以他们在击打后，要把踩槌头保持压在鼓皮上
[EN]Then It's kind like, it's the same thing when you bury the stick into the head
[CN]那么，这就像你把鼓槌压在鼓皮上一样
[EN]Which some drummer do, would go results, if you don't have proper technique
[CN]有些鼓手却是这样打，如果你没有运用适当的技巧，这样行不通的
[EN]I'm trying to do, I have to pay a attention to currence physical lost, otherwise you're gonna kill yourself
[CN]我也试过，我必须注意力量回馈。不然你就是在自虐
[EN]I'm lazy in nature, So I use techniques to help me out[CN]我根性很懒，所以我选择用技巧来帮我忙
[EN]I've noticed that you decet bass drum pedals
[CN]我注意到你最近在拆踩槌
[EN]Yeah yeah very neurotically for about 10 years
[CN]对呀对呀，非常神经质的拆了10多年了
[EN]Like said that I'm coming to crisis like a way which is gonna clapse very soon
[CN]因为我觉得存在一种危机，这些旧观念不久就会崩盘
[EN]And then I think I'll have some answers for you know I talked to a lot of people
[CN]我相信我最终会给你们一些答案的，我跟很多人聊过这些
[EN]And I still do, you know it's like it started to think you know
[CN]我现在仍然在拆踩槌做研究，我就像你开始..
[EN]Once you started to put question mark, or exchange information point with question mark, then Ok this is people like take this for granted, if it really true, you know
[CN]一旦你开始在出现问号，把认为习以为常的信息换成大大的问号，他们真的对么？
[EN]Then you, you might end up yeah it is or not it's bogus , why have I doing that, nobody question that you know it's not necessarily create the best gear, but they create what's request, so you know, people have to be educated
[CN]接下来，你可能得到两种结果，是的，的确对，或许是否定的，根本不是这么回事，我为什么要做这些呢？，没有人会质疑厂商应该制作最好的设备，但是事实厂商是迎合制作鼓手要求制作的，所以，真像要大白于世
[EN]Some trying off my 15 cents, we are looking forward to that
[CN]我试着尽我所能去揭开真相，我们大家都很期待哦
[EN]Be patient, I appreciate your time, thank you very much, just be patient this project
[CN]大家要淡定，淡定..谢谢你花时间接受采访，十分感谢，对于这个新教程，大家要有耐心
[EN]It's tsunami, this very scary thing, that it's coming I did it before I'll look, will be alright
[CN]这就像山崩海啸一样，我现在还很害怕，但是它会上市的,对么？没错，我之前已经做过了，我们拭目以待吧